http://www.allaboutvision.com/privacy.htm

Home » AllAboutVision.com Privacy Information"
Privacy Statement
By All About Vision
AllAboutVision.com’s policy is to respect the privacy of visitors to our website. This privacy statement describes how and why we gather information from our site’s visitors and what we do with it.Your personal data means any information relating to you, in particular your name and contact details such as your home address, your telephone number or your email address.Please take the time to read this privacy statement, as it is important that you understand how we are using your personal data and how we are protecting your privacy.If you have any questions regarding our use of your personal data, you can contact us:— Email: admin@allaboutvision.com— Postal mail: All About Vision, 5215 N. O'Connor Blvd, 11th Floor, Irving, TX 75039How we collect dataOur web server, like all web servers, will automatically recognize each visitor’s internet address (or “IP address”). This does not provide us with personally identifiable information. Our server logs will record page views and the serving of images and other files, and can associate those actions with particular visitor sessions.On certain pages, you may have the opportunity to provide personally identifiable information. When you voluntarily provide us with information about yourself, you consent to our use of your personal information in accordance with this policyData we collect when you visit our websiteWhen you access our website, we automatically collect and store some of your data in our server logs and in cookies, which are small files we sent to your computer when you visit our website.This data does not allow us to directly identify you; however, it records data related to your browsing on our website, such as pages that you accessed, the date and time you accessed these pages, your search queries, information on your device (hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifier, internet protocol address, hardware settings, browser type, browser language), the date and time of your request and referral URL.We may use third-party advertising companies or affiliates to display advertisements on our website. These third-party advertising companies or affiliates may separately place or recognize a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to AllAboutVision.com. We cannot see the information collected or stored in third-party cookies. We do not provide data about you to these third-party advertisers.You can opt out of the collection of your personal data when you visit AllAboutVision.com. To do this, you will need to configure your browser to not accept cookies (for information, refer to the “help” section of your web browser).Data we collect when you sign up for offersSome of the services offered on our website require you to sign up for them. If you want to use these services, we will ask you to provide us with personal data, and we thank you for providing us with complete and accurate data. Please inform us, too, if your data needs to be updated.If you do not provide us with complete and accurate data, or if you do not inform us that your data needs to be updated, we may not be able to provide you with the services you requested.We continue to evolve the services offered on AllAboutVision.com and may in the future collect the following categories of your personal data:— Identification data, including your name, telephone number, email address, home address, login and password, photograph and date of birth (or age).— IT data, including data related to your browsing on our website, such as the pages that you accessed, the date and time you accessed these pages, your search queries, information on your device (hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, internet protocol address, hardware settings, browser type, browser language), the date and time of your request and referral URL.How we use the personal data we collectWe only use your personal data within the limits authorized by the laws and regulation.We do not make any automated decisions solely on automatic processing which may produce legal effects concerning you, or similarly significantly affect you.We use your personal data for the following purposes:— Marketing services: We may use your identification data to facilitate delivery of marketing offers and services. — Website improvements: We anonymize your IT data and use it to improve your experience on our website, identify and report any bugs and issues, assess the impact of changes we make on customer behavior, analyze and improve the performance of the website. Such a process is operated for our legitimate interest.How long we keep personal data we collectThe period for which we store your personal data is detailed below:Category data and retention period— Identification data, excluding ophthalmic prescription and medical data: 12 years— IT data: 12 years— Financial data: This is not stored on any of our systems.Personal data we shareWe inform you that we may share your personal data with affiliated entities (members of the Essilor Group).— Identification data: Online transaction processing, order fulfilment marketing, promotional communications, order analysis – worldwide— IT data: Analyzing customer website and purchase behavior and other data available for marketing and promotional communications – worldwideHow we protect personal dataWe have measures in place to protect your personal data against unauthorized access, use or disclosure, including without limitation:We implement and maintain sophisticated technical measures to ensure that your personal data is recorded and processed in complete confidentiality and security.We restrict access to your personal data and monitor the access, use and transfer of personal data.All of our employees who have access to your personal data are required to enter into non-disclosure or similar agreements, which imposes obligations on them to comply with our data privacy and confidentiality requirements.We require any business partners and third-party service providers with whom we may share your personal data to comply with any applicable data privacy and confidentiality requirements.We provide data privacy training on a regular basis to our employees and third parties who have access to personal data.What rights you haveUnder applicable data protection laws and regulations, you have the right:To access, rectify and or erase your personal data.To restrict or object to the processing of your data information.To tell us that you do not want to receive marketing information.To require us to transfer some of your personal data (in certain circumstances) to you or a third party.We are committed to enable you to exercise your rights: To do so, you can contact us by email or postal mail (as detailed above). Please provide the following information when exercising your data privacy rights:— Your full name, contact information and a photocopy of your identity card.— Your specific data privacy request (in other words, what rights you want to exercise).— The date of the application and your signature (if you sent your application by postal mail).If you do not get satisfaction by contacting us, you can lodge a complaint about our processing of your personal data with a data protection authority.Changes to this privacy notice
We at AllAboutVision.com regularly review our compliance with our privacy statement, in particular to make it compliant with new laws and regulations regarding data protection. Though this privacy statement may change from time to time, we will not reduce your rights without your explicit consent.Do we use cookies?Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites' or service providers' systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember you, understanding and saving your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. Our commitment to youThank you for turning to and relying on AllAboutVision.com to learn about eye conditions, eyeglasses, sunglasses contacts and overall eye health. Thank you, too, for reading this privacy statement outlining how we protect your personal data.
Page updated June 2019
Schedule an exam
Find Eye Doctor
Hot Topics
Face shields, eye goggles advised to prevent COVID-19 spread
What does the average eye exam cost without insurance?
Infographic: How much do eye exams cost?
How to get rid of bags under your eyes
Coronavirus: How eyes may play a role in its spread
Eye doctors add safety measures to cut COVID-19 risk
A face mask reduces coronavirus transmission but doesn't protect the eyes
The importance of healthy vision for road safety
